tracked.com 2011-10-11

# Privacy Policy - Hashable.com

Last Updated: June 1, 2010 

Your privacy, and the privacy of all registered users of Hashable.com ("Hashable.com" or the "Website"), is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice and choice in the collection and use of information regarding our users and their activities at our site. 

This policy tells you what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at [privacy@hashable.com ](mailto:%20privacy@hashable.com) or at the mailing address set forth below if you have any questions regarding its content. 

In connection with your use of the Website and the services provided in connection with the Website (such services and Website, collectively, the "Service"), we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in the following ways. 

## Log Data

Our servers may automatically record non-personally identifiable information ("Log Data") from anyone who uses our service or comes to our Website. This Log Data may include your IP address, browser type, referring domain, pages visited, visit duration and submitted search terms. This data is used to monitor and assist in improvements to the Service. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the Website based on your preferences and activities as determined based upon such Log Data. 

## Registration and Account Data

If you register to use the Website, we ask for and store information you provide such as your email, first name, last name, username, industry, job title, company, gender, country, postal code, photo and a brief description of yourself. Only email, first name, last name, username, postal code and country are required entries. Your email address will only be displayed if you elect to do so through your Account Settings page. 

After you register to use the Website, may set up your personal profile, form relationships, and transmit information through various channels ("Account Data"). We collect this information so that we can provide you the Service and offer personalized features, including varying the content you receive in future visits to the Website based on your preferences and activities. We may retain such Account Data so that, for instance, you can return to view prior interactions you've had or easily see your contact list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time. 

## Combination of Log Data and Registration Data

Log Data may be combined with a user's username and Account Data once a user has registered or subsequently logged into the Website. The combined data is used to monitor and assist in improvements to the Service, and will not be shared with third parties except in the case of third party service providers and legal processes, as noted below. 

## Cookies

Use of certain features on Hashable.com requires that you accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that our Website sends to your browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at our Website and better serve your needs and interests as noted above. 

Third party ads displayed on Hashable.com may also contain cookies set by the advertiser, ad network or their agent. Hashable.com does not control these cookies. Users of Hashable.com should consult the privacy policies of the advertiser, ad network or their agent to learn how they use cookies. 

## Submitted Content

You post content on Website at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of content you post may remain viewable in cached and archived pages on the Internet or if other Users have copied or stored content you post. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Hashable.com is a violation of the Hashable.com Terms of Service and should be reported via [ feedback@hashable.com](mailto:feedback@hashable.com). 

## Inviting Others

When you use our service via email to capture a meeting, introduction, referral, or other activity, you will be sending us the email addresses or Twitter handles of the meeting participants, or introduced/referred parties (aka " s"). If the Recipients are not already registered, we will send them an email confirming their passive participation in Hashable and inviting them to visit the Website, where they will have the opportunity to create an account and delete or adjust site-wide privacy settings regarding any information directly related to themselves. Hashable.com stores the Recipient email address information to track interactions, send invitations and reminders, and to track the success of our referral program. The Recipient may [ contact us](mailto:feedback@hashable.com) through the Website to request that we remove this information from our database in the event that they do not want to create an account and actively control their site-wide privacy settings. Hashable does not publicly display or provide to third parties the complete email address of non-registered users. 

Without any contact from the person whose email or Twitter handle you provided, we will display any information involving them (as provided by you) as dictated by the privacy settings you have applied to your own account. All users are advised to use discretion in the type of information they provide publicly about other people and all users provide such information solely at their own risk. 

## Profile Information

When you register with Hashable.com, you create your own profile and privacy settings regarding your activity stream. If you are logged in, you can go to the profile settings page to adjust your privacy settings. We use your personally identifying information to identify and register you as a user of the Website and to customize the various features of the Website according to your interests, activities and preferences. 

Profile information is used by Hashable.com primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others, based on your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., another user has included you in a meeting, introduction or referral, and you have not prevented the display or supplementation of such information via your privacy settings), other Hashable.com users may be able to supplement your profile. 

Your name, company, profile picture, and geographic location will be available in Hashable search results. These limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends and community can find you. 

If you elect to make such information private and not searchable via your account settings, such information may persist in our backup copies, and/or on the Internet via search engines' cached search results until such time as such search engines update their search results. 

## Legal Compliance

We may disclose information to fulfill legal or regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or to prevent harm. 

## Third Party Service Providers

We retain certain third party service providers to perform functions and services to us. We may share your personal information with these third party service providers, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and services, and only pursuant to obligations that are no less restrictive than those contained in this privacy policy. 

## Security

Hashable uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard personally identifying information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

## Minimum Age

Users of Hashable must be at least 13 years of age. We do not knowingly accept registrations from users that are under 13. We will delete accounts of any users that we find to be under-age. If you are aware that a child under the age of 13 has become a registered user, please inform us at privacy@hashable.com, so that we can confirm and take the appropriate steps to remove the account and any related information. 

## Communication

Hashable.com may send you account activity-related announcements from time to time. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message through your account, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. You have the option of opting out of notifications regarding the actions of other users (for example, user meeting notifications and user message notifications) through your account settings.Hashable.com reserves the right to send you Hashable.com service and legal notices about your account. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations, and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this Website. This policy was posted on June 1, 2010. Data will be handled in accordance with the policy in effect at the time the data is used. 

Our mailing address is: 

Hashable, Inc.   
989 Ave. of the Americas   
16th Floor   
New York, NY 10018   
United States
